<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tarot Handbook</string>
<!--    Layout string resources. -->
    <string name="title_placeholder">Title</string>
    <string name="fragment_handbook_label">Handbook</string>
    <string name="fragment_tell_label">Tell Fortunes</string>
    <string name="fragment_options_label">Options</string>
    <string name="tell_fortune_btn_text">Tell Fortune</string>
<!--    Arcana -->
    <string name="major">Major arcana</string>
    <string name="cups">Cups</string>
    <string name="wands">Wands</string>
    <string name="swords">Swords</string>
    <string name="pentacles">Pentacles</string>
<!--    Names and interpretations of cards.-->
    <string name="title_fool">The Fool</string>
    <string name="interpretation_fool">Without the notion of Zero, our system of mathematics
        becomes meaningless. Similarly, the Fool is an essential part of the Tarot because he is
        the spark that sets everything else into motion, the divine breath that gives life and
        inspires the first step towards fulfillment and completion. Though the first step down a
        long path may often seem small in comparison to the journey, that first step is vital
        because without it there would be no journey at all! The Fool is the cause behind all
        effects, the power behind all manifestations and the seeds of the end sown in every
        beginning.\n\nThe Fool is unmoulded potential, pure and innocent, neither positive nor negative yet containing the possibility of both. He is the unconditioned soul about to come into manifestation for the first time to start learning the lessons of the world. Though everyone calls him a Fool, he does not pay them any attention, and he simply goes on his way. Certainly what they say can be justified, since his ignorance of the world can lead him to do things that more experienced people would never imagine. But in these things he can find knowledge and enlightenment. He does not care what others think or say about him, because he knows that what he is doing is right for him.\n\nHis approach to life is a strange, unconventional one, because he does what is comfortable to him. This is a viewpoint not often supported in our modern world, in which \"do as I say\" is the commandment most followed. To those who have lived their life under this philosophy, the approach of the Fool may be extravagant, shocking, even frightening. But this approach is all that the Fool knows, and because the only approval he requires is his own, he will continue to live this way, despite what all others think of him. He has total faith in himself. Perhaps he is not such a fool after all.\n\nThe Fool does not hide himself from the light, because he is the light - the wonderful light that shines out of every child before they see the world and are forced to build so many walls and barriers to protect themselves. The innocence of a child, sadly, is something rarely found outside of children, even though a lot of people could use it these days. With this innocence comes perfect trust, fearlessness in others, and total self-reliance. It allows you to see the world with new eyes and learn new things every day of your life. Think of how much better the world would be if everybody acted this way! It\'s a shame that only children, and the Fool, see this light.\n\nThe Fool almost always stands for new beginnings, new experiences and new choices; the first steps along a new path and the first words written onto a blank page. Like the Aces of the Minor Arcana, such beginnings are like the Fool himself - neither positive nor negative, but with the potential to turn into either, depending on the choices you make and the path you follow. But this must not be your concern, because when a journey begins no one can know (or should know) what will happen on the way to the destination. Never let another person control your life. Live in the present and trust in your own abilities - this is the way of the Fool.\n\nSuch journeys always imply a degree of risk, and hence the Fool is pictured walking toward the edge of a high cliff. With any new experience there is always the risk of failure and the certainty of change; it is the degree of change, and how that change will appear, that are undeterminable. But the Fool has no qualms about taking chances, so why should you? It is through the first steps that we learn how to walk, and it is through changes that we learn how to live our lives in harmony and peace. So jump head first into the abyss of the unknown, and know that even if you eventually fall to the ground, for a while you will soar.</string>
    <string name="title_magician">The Magician</string>
    <string name="interpretation_magician">The Magician\'s number is One, the number of creation
        and individuality; his power is transformation through the use of his will. In his
        manipulation of the basic elements into all the substances and materials of life, he
        shows us that from a foundation of the mundane can emerge all that is to come. He can
        take the Nothing from which the Fool emerged and shape it into Something, making one out
        of zero. Clearly this is power of a divine sort, and it is true that the Magician is a
        conduit for a higher power, which commands all of the material world. Since all that we
        can see in the physical world is the conduit himself, the acts he performs often seem
        like magic.\n\nThe Magician may seem like a strange title for someone who holds real
        power, because the word \"magician\" tends to conjure up pictures of illusionists and
        escape artists, whose power involves sleight of hand and misdirection. The Magician,
        however, is similar to the stage illusionist in many ways. He is confident in his skills
        and his ability to produce the effects that he wants. His real power comes from sources
        outside of him, and he is powerless without these sources, just as an illusionist depends
        on people \"behind the scenes\". Both magician and Magician, however, are as important to
        their powers are the powers are to them. Without a conduit, power itself is impotent and
        useless.\n\nWith his powers the Magician holds influence over all - theory and practice,
        logic and emotion, thought and action. Almost every modern depiction of the Magician
        includes one or more symbols of infinity to denote his limitless power; the snake eating
        its tail and the lemniscate (horizontal figure-eight) being chief among these. This
        limitless power comes from sources outside his body yet under his control. And as long as
        the Magician remembers that this power is his to command, even if he loses all of his
        worldly power and skill he can never truly be called powerless. For his Will is a power that, while it can be subdued, it can never be destroyed.\n\nAnother nearly universal association with the Magician is the red-and-white color scheme. This theme recurs throughout the Tarot and it is very symbolic that it starts with this card and not the Fool. For while the Fool was the potential for positive and negative, the Magician is the union of positive and negative. He creates and he preserves; he destroys and he redeems. His true power is that he not only knows what he must do, but he knows how he must do it, and why he must do it. Then he does it. The Magician reminds us that a wish alone will change nothing, but a decision can change everything. A desire to create is nothing without an ability to create, and vice-versa.\n\nWhen the Magician appears he shows that you are ready to become a conduit for power, like he is. The forces of creation and destruction have always been at your command but now you have the wisdom and confidence needed to use them constructively. Now is the time to act, if you know what is it you want to accomplish and why. Since the powers of transformation are at your command, change your desires into objectives, your thoughts into actions, your goals into achievements. If you have recently met with failure, now you can change that failure into success as easily as the Magician changes fire into water. The only limits you have are those you impose on yourself.\n\nThe outward manifestations of such power are as numerous as they are varied, but the most common outer effect of the Magician\'s influence is unswaying and total confidence. The realization that the world is under your control is what inspires this kind of confidence, and with good reason. So go out into the world, set your mind to whatever goal you are interested in, and then just stand back and watch as everything falls into place under your command. Ultimately, the message of the Magician is a simple one despite his limitless and infinitely complex power. Your life is under your control. Your life is what you want it to be. Your life is what you make it.</string>
    <string name="title_high_priestess">The High Priestess</string>
    <string name="interpretation_high_priestess">The High Priestess is arguably the most
        difficult of the Major Arcana to qualify with words alone, because so much of her power
        and ability is veiled in mystery that it is difficult for anyone to fathom it all. Every
        card in the Tarot speaks differently to everyone, but the Priestess seems to bear the
        widest range of interpretations, because she speaks directly to the Inner Voice, the
        unconscious mind. She is the manifestation of the unconscious and the effects of the
        mysterious in our everyday world. Trying to see how such mysteries work often defeats
        their purpose, and with this in mind, the High Priestess will be explained in as much
        detail as possible.\n\nShe is, above all else, the base of potential that is the source of the power wielded by the Magician. She is the unlimited potential that allows him to transform and create whatever his Will desires. Understanding this type of balance, as found between potential and creation, masculine and feminine, is the key to unlocking some of the mysteries of the High Priestess. We see the clear progression of the theme of balance; instead of integrating opposites, the Priestess keeps them separate and keeps them in balance nonetheles. She herself is the scales; this symbolism is found in many Tarot decks. Without this balance there can be no power.\n\nThe second symbolic motif found in almost all instances of the High Priestess are symbols of the
        unconscious mind. On the Rider-Waite version this motif is especially prominent, but most
        decks feature at least some lunar imagery that in turn has ties to the unconscious. Most
        decks that have the \"twin pillars\" symbology also depict a veil strung between those
        pillars; the High Priestess stands between us and that veil as a moderator. Behind the
        veil lies the powers of the unconscious, which we cannot start to understand but which,
        through her, we can learn to control. She is the gateway to realms that we may never
        fully comprehend or master.\n\nWhile it would be impossible for anyone to learn all of
        her mysteries and secrets, the High Priestess remains as a guide to those of us willing
        to venture deep within our minds to discover the true powers hidden deep inside each of
        us. This is the same power as that depicted on the Magician, but the scope of the
        Priestess\' power is far different. While the Magician focuses his powers outward, to
        achieve a meaningful effect on the world, the High Priestess shows us that we can also
        use these powers on an inner level, to enrich and transform ourselves. Such transformations are certainly not as dramatic as the Magician\'s, but they are almost always more powerful.\n\nThe High Priestess represents the mysteries of the unconscious and the Inner Voice, and her appearance is often a sign that your own intuition is trying to send you a message. The unconscious often speaks to us in symbols, so be alert around you for anything that seems out of the ordinary. This said, if you have an important decision to make when the Priestess appears, this is often a sign that the answers will be revealed to you, if you are patient and open to the whispers from within. You simply have to wait and be receptive to inner messages. Her lesson is that everything you need to know already exists within you.\n\nThe theme of dualism in the High Priestess cannot be avoided either. She is often a sign of the
        Shadow, the negative portion of your personality that no one sees, and that you yourself could be unaware of. (In this sense, the term \'negative\' does not refer to evil, just the opposite polarity from the positive and expressive part of your personality.) If you accept the Shadow within you, its powers will be open to you if you wish to use them. In most people the Shadow side is the more passive of the two, and the Priestess can therefore advocate a need for passivity in a situation. It is not always necessary to act; sometimes goals can be realized through inaction.</string>
    <string name="title_empress">The Empress</string>
    <string name="interpretation_empress">The Empress represents a departure from the dualistic
        philosophy of the first three Major Arcana, as well as from the strongly spiritual
        teachings of those three cards. Rather than simple dichotomies of positive and negative,
        the Tarot now starts dealing with the unfication of spirit, mind and body. The Empress is
        the latter leg of this triad, representing the physical body and the material world. From her comes all the pleasure of the senses and the abundance of life in all its forms. She is also the mother archetype, and through her we get a first glimpse of the power of love in the Tarot.\n\nThe world of the Empress is an ideal and perfectly beautiful place, totally natural, untouched by artificial colors, lights or sounds. This is a place of bounty and fertility, a living representation of the process of creation and birth that the Empress herself symbolizes. She doesn\'t just live in this place, she is this place, just as much as the Priestess is the balance that keeps apart positive and negative. The Empress is no less beautiful than the flowers that throw their scent across her fields, no less fertile than the soil that lies underneath her throne. If anything represents the idea of Mother Earth in the Tarot, then it is the Empress.\n\nHer primary power, like the two Arcana before her, is the power of creation. But her creation is not based on creating the world she wishes to live in, or the person she wants to be, because she has that world and is that person. She creates life in all its myriad forms. The Empress is the archetype of the mother, the ultimate creator and giver of life; thus her associations can be extended beyond creativity into fertility, pregnancy and the daunting task of motherhood, which she always faces with a smile and a happy heart. She takes pleasure in all things, particularly her own creations - and everything in nature is her own creation.\n\nTying into the theme of motherhood is the notion of unconditional love, which the Empress also represents. She makes no demands, sets no conditions, just loves everything equally and with all the power she can. From this, it can be said, derives her only real weakness, and it is something that all mothers deal with at some point. She is often over-protective of her creations, and wishes no harm to come to them at all. That would disrupt the eternal bliss and happiness of her realm. But as it is, the realm of the Empress is both the picture of beauty and of stagnation. So while the Empress\' love can make you feel as secure as if we are in your mother\'s arms, it can also turn into a prison if experienced for too long.\n\nWhen the Empress appears in your life, you should make special effort to open up to her perfect and unconditional love. In that way you can become more like her: gentle and affectionate, gracious and elegant. Such qualities are often neglected, but they are also useful in a world of harshness and apathy. So instead of plodding through life, take some time to celebrate it! The Empress can often herald the conception or the birth of a child, and in that circumstance there is even greater reason to celebrate. Inspire others to do the same; the Empress is a leader, and the power she holds over other people is firm, but loving. Know this and lead as she would.\n\nKnow also that the perfectly abundant world of the Empress is always free for you to enjoy. Even if you know that you have to go back to the \"real world\" eventually, a vacation from the hectic and artificial life that most people live these days will certainly be welcome. Spend some time outdoors, in the fresh air, enjoying every aspect of creation. And then, when you go back to where you were, the Empress\' creative power and beauty will remain to inspire you and give you power. Strengthen your innate connection with the Earth\'s creativity and you will, by association, strengthen your own creative power. Cultivate your creativity and plants the seeds of a bountiful harvest.</string>
    <string name="title_emperor">The Emperor</string>
    <string name="interpretation_emperor">The second leg of the Body-Mind-Spirit triad is the
        Emperor, representing the power of the mind to shape the world. Such action does not take
        place at the command of the will, but through the command of the spoken or written word.
        The Emperor is the representation - and the ruler - of the structured and regulated
        world. This is an ideal world like the Empress\', though one that is not always as beautiful or lavish. But just because it is more harsh does not mean it is any less necessary to enlightenment; on the contrary, it is completely necessary to balance Mind and Body, male and female.\n\nThe Emperor is the opposite of the Empress in many ways. She is the Mother, he is the archetypal Father, wise in the ways of the world and knowledgeable of how to live as part of a structure along with everyone else. The Emperor does have a strong and powerful heart, as every father should, but he shows this side of himself through the imposition of strict guidelines and rules, as most fathers do. If anything he is even more protective than the Empress, because he has created order from chaos and wishes nothing to disturb that order. Underneath his royal robes hides the suit of armor which he proudly wears when defending those under his protection.\n\nThe Emperor teaches us many things, the first of which being that every rule has an application and a reason for being. If we can understand this, then his world may not seem so restrictive after all. In fact, all restriction is ultimately for your own good, because without the law and order that this card so powerfully symbolizes, the world would fall into anarchy. Government and law both draw their power from him, but unlike the governmental figures that we hear so much about in modern times, the Emperor cannot be corrupted by power. He rules like King Arthur, who brought together the warring powers of England and knit them into the greatest empire the world has ever known.\n\nHe is truly the master of his realm, and he rules with a firm hand, but a just one. He will listen to the counsel of others, though the final decision is always his. War is one of his many tools and he will not hesitate to use violence to protect those he cares about. The privileged few who are subject to his protection always repay him with the loyalty and respect he deserves. But the Emperor\'s power does not only extend to the controlling of nations. He is also the father, the male role model who offers advice, sets direction and brings security. He takes what he has learned, and passes it on to the next generation, so someday they can be as wise and powerful as he is.\n\nAny of the Major Arcana can represent people, but the Emperor is the kind of energy that often manifests in the form of a person. Obviously all kinds of leaders and fathers will harbor some of his influence, but he can also show someone who acts like a father by setting tone and imposing structure. He is a regulating force and thus associated with the government, bureaucracy and the legal system; his appearance often indicates an encouter with one or more of these systems. The Emperor can also personify the assumption of power and control, by you or someone close to you. If you are the one in power, take care that you always use it wisely.\n\nAbove all else, the Emperor shows the benefits of structure and logic ruling over the emotions and lesser desires. Often, domination of the mind over the heart is not wanted, but in some cases is it necessary and even welcomed. When hard choices must be made it\'s important to maintain your concentration and focus, and this is something the energy of the Emperor allows you to do. When he shows a part of you, let that part of you manifest and take control. Enjoy the assertiveness and confidence it brings. Forge ahead and do what you know is best. If you can master yourself then you should have little problem mastering the world and all the things in it.</string>
    <string name="title_hierophant">The Hierophant</string>
    <string name="interpretation_hierophant">Spirit is the final leg of the triad that has been
        previously seen in the Empress and Emperor; the archetype of the spiritual world is the
        Hierophant. This is the card of beliefs, both religious and otherwise, though it does
        tend to focus on the religious and spiritual aspects because the Hierophant himself is
        often depicted as a holy man. Indeed, in some decks this card is known as the Pope or High Priest. But in actuality, a Hierophant is a person who holds \'forbidden\' or \'secret\' knowledge. While this could easily apply to the clergy, it has far greater scope than this. In a way it could be said that (with apologies to Crowley) every man and every woman is a Hierophant.\n\nThe Hierophant can even stand for groups of more than one person, and in the majority of cases he is better represented by an institution than by a single person. This is because his is the power of the group and the society, who change the world to fit their beliefs. The same theme of control and change that first appeared with the Magician continues here in its fifth iteration; now there is still a well-defined leader, but the people do not follow him because they are ordered to. They follow because they are part of the group. The main philosophies of the Hierophant are that there\'s no \"I\" in \"team\", and that the good of the many outweighs the good of the one.\n\nSuch a philosophy may seem unnecessarily restrictive but, as the Emperor has taught us, restriction leads to order. The Hierophant is charged with the maintenance and propagation of tradition and conventional beliefs, and anyone who goes against these beliefs is shunned. Balance and conformity are the goals of the Hierophant, and neither positive nor negative is emphasized - only tradition matters. In extreme cases, this can indeed have very negative effects (as Galileo found out) but in most cases having some tradition to follow is beneficial. The traditions and ceremonies of the church, which are particularly strong in this card, are a prime example of this.\n\nOn a more personal level, the Hierophant is also a teacher or a mentor. One major role of a spiritual leader is to initiate others into the community and teach them the ways of the group. Obviously one who holds the secrets and is entrusted with the traditions of the group is a prime candidate to teach them to others, and the Hierophant plays this role well. Though his approach to teaching is one that centers on conformity and shuns individual expression for the moment, this can be helpful. Only once the student has mastered the ways of the group can he or she properly decide whether to remain or leave.\n\nWhen the Hierophant appears it will often be in the form of a teacher or a mentor, who instructs you in the ways of his particular belief in the hopes that you will join him. Such teachers do not have to be of a spiritual or mystical background; an employer training a new employee in the operation of a business is as much a Hierophant as any religious teacher. If your current situation seems to require more experience then you can call upon, be open to the presence of a teacher or mentor in your life. But do not make the grave mistake of openly seeking such a teacher - as the old proverb says, when the student is ready, the teacher will appear.\n\nThe Hierophant can also represent group activities and beliefs, and in either case, support of the establishment and respect for the rules are emphasized. So if you are planning something revolutionary, the repeated appearance of the Hierophant is a good sign to forget such action and go with the flow for the time being. The traditional way of doing things must work most of the time, or else it wouldn\'t have been around long enough to become tradition! However, when an idea is proven wrong it is certainly time for a change. The true Hierophant is one who has a deep respect for his beliefs, but who will not blindly follow them to his own ruin.</string>
</resources>