<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tarot Handbook</string>
    <string name="title_fool">The Fool</string>
    <string name="interpretation_fool">Without the notion of Zero, our system of mathematics
        becomes meaningless. Similarly, the Fool is an essential part of the Tarot because he is
        the spark that sets everything else into motion, the divine breath that gives life and
        inspires the first step towards fulfillment and completion. Though the first step down a
        long path may often seem small in comparison to the journey, that first step is vital
        because without it there would be no journey at all! The Fool is the cause behind all
        effects, the power behind all manifestations and the seeds of the end sown in every
        beginning.\n\nThe Fool is unmoulded potential, pure and innocent, neither positive nor negative yet containing the possibility of both. He is the unconditioned soul about to come into manifestation for the first time to start learning the lessons of the world. Though everyone calls him a Fool, he does not pay them any attention, and he simply goes on his way. Certainly what they say can be justified, since his ignorance of the world can lead him to do things that more experienced people would never imagine. But in these things he can find knowledge and enlightenment. He does not care what others think or say about him, because he knows that what he is doing is right for him.\n\nHis approach to life is a strange, unconventional one, because he does what is comfortable to him. This is a viewpoint not often supported in our modern world, in which \"do as I say\" is the commandment most followed. To those who have lived their life under this philosophy, the approach of the Fool may be extravagant, shocking, even frightening. But this approach is all that the Fool knows, and because the only approval he requires is his own, he will continue to live this way, despite what all others think of him. He has total faith in himself. Perhaps he is not such a fool after all.\n\nThe Fool does not hide himself from the light, because he is the light - the wonderful light that shines out of every child before they see the world and are forced to build so many walls and barriers to protect themselves. The innocence of a child, sadly, is something rarely found outside of children, even though a lot of people could use it these days. With this innocence comes perfect trust, fearlessness in others, and total self-reliance. It allows you to see the world with new eyes and learn new things every day of your life. Think of how much better the world would be if everybody acted this way! It\'s a shame that only children, and the Fool, see this light.\n\nThe Fool almost always stands for new beginnings, new experiences and new choices; the first steps along a new path and the first words written onto a blank page. Like the Aces of the Minor Arcana, such beginnings are like the Fool himself - neither positive nor negative, but with the potential to turn into either, depending on the choices you make and the path you follow. But this must not be your concern, because when a journey begins no one can know (or should know) what will happen on the way to the destination. Never let another person control your life. Live in the present and trust in your own abilities - this is the way of the Fool.\n\nSuch journeys always imply a degree of risk, and hence the Fool is pictured walking toward the edge of a high cliff. With any new experience there is always the risk of failure and the certainty of change; it is the degree of change, and how that change will appear, that are undeterminable. But the Fool has no qualms about taking chances, so why should you? It is through the first steps that we learn how to walk, and it is through changes that we learn how to live our lives in harmony and peace. So jump head first into the abyss of the unknown, and know that even if you eventually fall to the ground, for a while you will soar.</string>
    <string name="major">Major arcana</string>
    <string name="title_magician">The Magician</string>
    <string name="interpretation_magician">The Magician\'s number is One, the number of creation
        and individuality; his power is transformation through the use of his will. In his
        manipulation of the basic elements into all the substances and materials of life, he
        shows us that from a foundation of the mundane can emerge all that is to come. He can
        take the Nothing from which the Fool emerged and shape it into Something, making one out
        of zero. Clearly this is power of a divine sort, and it is true that the Magician is a
        conduit for a higher power, which commands all of the material world. Since all that we
        can see in the physical world is the conduit himself, the acts he performs often seem
        like magic.\n\nThe Magician may seem like a strange title for someone who holds real
        power, because the word \"magician\" tends to conjure up pictures of illusionists and
        escape artists, whose power involves sleight of hand and misdirection. The Magician,
        however, is similar to the stage illusionist in many ways. He is confident in his skills
        and his ability to produce the effects that he wants. His real power comes from sources
        outside of him, and he is powerless without these sources, just as an illusionist depends
        on people \"behind the scenes\". Both magician and Magician, however, are as important to
        their powers are the powers are to them. Without a conduit, power itself is impotent and
        useless.\n\nWith his powers the Magician holds influence over all - theory and practice,
        logic and emotion, thought and action. Almost every modern depiction of the Magician
        includes one or more symbols of infinity to denote his limitless power; the snake eating
        its tail and the lemniscate (horizontal figure-eight) being chief among these. This
        limitless power comes from sources outside his body yet under his control. And as long as
        the Magician remembers that this power is his to command, even if he loses all of his
        worldly power and skill he can never truly be called powerless. For his Will is a power that, while it can be subdued, it can never be destroyed.\n\nAnother nearly universal association with the Magician is the red-and-white color scheme. This theme recurs throughout the Tarot and it is very symbolic that it starts with this card and not the Fool. For while the Fool was the potential for positive and negative, the Magician is the union of positive and negative. He creates and he preserves; he destroys and he redeems. His true power is that he not only knows what he must do, but he knows how he must do it, and why he must do it. Then he does it. The Magician reminds us that a wish alone will change nothing, but a decision can change everything. A desire to create is nothing without an ability to create, and vice-versa.\n\nWhen the Magician appears he shows that you are ready to become a conduit for power, like he is. The forces of creation and destruction have always been at your command but now you have the wisdom and confidence needed to use them constructively. Now is the time to act, if you know what is it you want to accomplish and why. Since the powers of transformation are at your command, change your desires into objectives, your thoughts into actions, your goals into achievements. If you have recently met with failure, now you can change that failure into success as easily as the Magician changes fire into water. The only limits you have are those you impose on yourself.\n\nThe outward manifestations of such power are as numerous as they are varied, but the most common outer effect of the Magician\'s influence is unswaying and total confidence. The realization that the world is under your control is what inspires this kind of confidence, and with good reason. So go out into the world, set your mind to whatever goal you are interested in, and then just stand back and watch as everything falls into place under your command. Ultimately, the message of the Magician is a simple one despite his limitless and infinitely complex power. Your life is under your control. Your life is what you want it to be. Your life is what you make it.</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>